(Howard:)Since we all agree
Episode I isn't our favourite,
(Howard:)maybe we just skip it this time.
Yeah, Howard,
I think you of all people
(Sheldon:)should avoid espousing
the principle
(Sheldon:)that if something
is not our favourite,
(Sheldon:)we should just get rid of it.
You know, I heard this way
of watching the movies
(Raj:)called the Machete Order,
where you watch Episodes IV and V,
(Raj:)then skip Episode I,
(Raj:)watch II and III
as a flashback,
(Raj:)and then finish with VI.
OK, so you'd lose
most of Jar Jar,
(Howard:)all the trade route talk,
and the boring senate hearings,
(Howard:)which are like watching C-SPAN
with monsters.
(Sheldon:)Get rid of the trade route part?
Then how would Palpatine
(Sheldon:)get Chancellor Valorum
kicked out of office?
(Sheldon:)How would he get
himself elected? How?
(Sheldon:)Can we get through one holiday
(Sheldon:)without you saying
something ridiculous?
(Raj:)It was just a suggestion.
(Sheldon:)Well, you know what else
was just a suggestion?
"Why don't we change
the Raisin Bran box?"
(Sheldon:)And you know
who got hurt by that?
(Sheldon:)Every single person
who eats breakfast!